Yeah, devs seem to be pretty good at
finding different types of hell. We had
framework hell, that was one. Tutorial
hell, that's another. And now we have
skill hell. Skill hell is where you try
all these different frameworks like GSD
and Spec kits and all this B mad and
stuff and you just try to cludge them
all together into something that works
and it doesn't. Now I know that I've
contributed a bit to skill hell because
I have a you know a set of skills out
there. Um but I think of my skills as
empowering the user, not empowering the
agent. I think what people are trying to
do right now is they're trying to take
software development processes and
encode them directly into the agent.
Whereas I think that you as the user,
you should be in control. You should
have your hand on the steering wheel and
I think that skills should be there to
help you, not necessarily help the
agent. In other words, you're encoding
your processes into repeatable things
that you can do again and again. So I
think skill hell is when you're just
smacking a bunch of stuff into the same
context window, a bunch of different
skills all at once, you know, not even
reading them, just trying to just check
if they work and it overloads the model
and you end up in sort of massive
context load. Whereas if you, the user,
are driving the skills, then you have
the feeling of control. You understand
each stage in the process. You can guide
the agent and you don't necessarily have
to stay in the loop for the whole thing.
You can still delegate to AFK, but you
are in control of the process, of the
loops. Yeah, from skill hell to skill
hala. Does that work?